Matt Hanbury

Pollard Lane, Leeds LS13 1EX

Tel: 079 4902 9191

Email: matthew.hanbury@outlook.com www.linkedin.com/in/matt-hanbury1

Highly adaptable and industry flexible with experience in administration, data handling and general office duties. An advanced user of Microsoft Office who is comfortable working in fast paced environments, working efficiently with set SLA's and taking proactive steps towards process improvement as well as problem solving.

Education

| Undergraduate | BBA Brand Building and Management – 2:1 (68.4%) |
|---|---|
| Vega School, Cape Town, South Africa (2012 – 2014) Internationally recognised tertiary education | Specific skills and knowledge areas: Micro, Macro and Development Economics Finance & Statistics with basic Accounting The critical study of brands and in-depth analysis of effective brand practice Undergoing briefs and conducting research, compiling data and presenting findings to key stakeholders with recommendations for practical and effective adjustments/improvements The study of acceptable organisational behaviour, critical thinking and creative development Innovation and Business Management |
| Michaelhouse | Main Matric subjects |
| Highschool, Balgowan, South Africa (2007 – 2011) | Economics (C), Geography (A), Computer Applications Technology (A) Matric (Equivalent to GCSEs and A-Levels combined) 3 subjects at grade A (including Geography, Computer applications Technology and Mathematical Literacy) 2 subjects at grade B (including English and Life Orientation) 2 subjects at grade C (including Afrikaans and Economics) |

Employment

| | Business Analyst |
|---|--|
| <u>Zenith – Intelligent</u> Vehicle Solutions | Role and specific skills: |
| 1 Great Exhibition Way, Kirkstall Forge, LS5 3BF Previous roles at Zenith: | Various detailed reporting P46/P11d audits & final reports Payroll audits & final reports Process improvements Daily communication with Customer Payroll managers, Customer Fleet contacts, Customer employees |
| Major Account Administrator | |
| Reservations Administrator | |

| | Customer Product Advisor |
|------------------------|--|
| <u>Get Geared</u> | Role and specific skills: |
| | Sales role focused on problem solving & customer satisfaction |
| 5 Regent Street, Leeds | Conveying large amounts of specific information to customers of |
| (June 2017 – March | varying mindsets and opinions |
| 2018) | Educating and informing customers in a highly efficient/concise |
| | manner in person and over the phone |
| | Negotiating price points, overcoming objections and eradicating |
| | doubts |
| | Creating, editing and closing customer accounts and sales orders |
| | Handling complaints and queries in person and over the phone |
| Hospitality Industry | Waiter/Barman |
| | The Original Oak – April 2018 – August 2018 |
| | Bill's Restaurant – September 2016 – June 2017 |
| | The Surbiton Flyer – March 2016 – June 2016 |
| | · |
| Fresh Advertising & | Account Executive Intern |
| <u>Marketing</u> | Role and specific skills: |
| | Attending weekly client meetings with my General Manager and |
| 235 Blaauwberg Rd, | assisting with the reporting of job brief status to clients |
| Table View, Cape Town | Liaising between specific clients and the agency with reference to job |
| (May 2015 – July 2015) | briefs and ad hoc requests |
| | On occasion delivering job reports to clients |
| | Undertaking general office admin and ad-hoc requests |
| Rhubeg Investments | Assistant Farm Manager |
| (Pty) Ltd | Role and specific skills: |
| | Gathering raw data on a daily basis from various flock sites |
| Rhubeg Farm, D16, | Uploading flock data into Ornithon FMS (Flock Management System) |
| Dargle, South Africa | Reviewing select data on a daily basis and immediately addressing any |
| (January 2015 – | issues |
| December 2015) | Reviewing other data on a weekly and monthly basis |
| | Retrieving data when required and displaying it in graphed formats |
| | Contributing to the immediate and forecasted decisions regarding |
| | flock management and the lifecycle of ± 1 000 000 fertile eggs |
| | produced monthly |
| | |
| | <u> </u> |